<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Journal</title>
    <link>narissara.lol/journal/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Journal</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 12 May 2022 16:51:43 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="narissara.lol/journal/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>2. To Every Thing There Is a Season</title>
      <link>narissara.lol/journal/posts/2/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2022 16:51:43 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>narissara.lol/journal/posts/2/</guid>
      <description>Dear Diary,
Isn’t it interesting that people are considered to become “adults” when they stop believing in Santa Clause? At what point I wonder, did our society associate maturity as someone who stop have faith, imagination, and belief in something magical? Why does “growing up” mean being cynical and jaded? Why can’t people believe in Santa Clause and be considered emotionally mature?
Or let’s reframe this question: there are people who believe in aliens, ghosts, zodiac signs, the supernatural, god and conspiracy theories- and those are seen as acceptable beliefs to possess.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>3. Powder</title>
      <link>narissara.lol/journal/posts/3/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2022 16:51:43 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>narissara.lol/journal/posts/3/</guid>
      <description>Dear Diary,
Powder is about the lack of relationship between a father and son. The father is irresponsible, unreliable, and tries to be adventurous. The son, as a result is placed in an adult role when he’s around his father.
I would say my relationship with my mother is similar to powder. Similarly, my mom took me out to a nightclub, and my father disapprove. Like the father, my mother is moody, and unstable.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>4. The Door</title>
      <link>narissara.lol/journal/posts/4/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2022 16:51:43 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>narissara.lol/journal/posts/4/</guid>
      <description>Dear Diary,
I would say the door speaks about the decay of happiness and intimate connections with other people over period of time. As the women go through stages of life, there are moments of weakness where darkness loom over her- and she fallen into depression.
Honestly, the more I think about it- the more the poem thinks about depression- and the constant battle to overcome it.
Sometimes, even when you are happy- the depression kicks in and the door swings open and close really quickly-that the person suffering from it don&amp;rsquo;t even notice.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>5. Simple Recipes </title>
      <link>narissara.lol/journal/posts/5/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2022 16:51:43 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>narissara.lol/journal/posts/5/</guid>
      <description>Dear Diary,
Hands can be both gentle and violent..Today class is interesting..As the teach mentioned, the story does seem to move back and froth in time.
I can see home, family, trauma, and broken love as a theme. I don&amp;rsquo;t know, this is a very hard story to hear in class.
I don&amp;rsquo;t like how this story is also about &amp;ldquo;cultural norms&amp;rdquo; and a conflict towards change through each generation. That&amp;rsquo;s bullshit, regardless of culture people should not be beating people.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>6. Tapka</title>
      <link>narissara.lol/journal/posts/6/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2022 16:51:43 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>narissara.lol/journal/posts/6/</guid>
      <description>Dear Diary,
Today class is interesting. Zac was so triggered by the teacher comment on being &amp;ldquo;prejudiced&amp;rdquo;.
Also the Russian girl in class is cute. I really want to date someone from Russia. I didn&amp;rsquo;t notice her until the teacher called her out to back up his argument.
Anyhow, I wasn&amp;rsquo;t surprised that Zac was pissed. Most LGBTQ+ people get livid-especially gay guys will go to war with anyone who even suggest or hint that they are closed-minded or stereotyping.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>7. Interpreter of Maladies </title>
      <link>narissara.lol/journal/posts/7/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2022 16:51:43 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>narissara.lol/journal/posts/7/</guid>
      <description>Communication is the main theme of the story. Or more precisely, the lack of it.
No one is communicating, not even Mr.Kapasi- and he works an an interpreter! He&amp;rsquo;s not talking to his wife, and continues to buy luxuries for his wife to avoid talking about their son death. They need to go to therapy and discuss how their son death affects them..or they really need to talk to each other.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>8. Cathedral</title>
      <link>narissara.lol/journal/posts/8/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2022 16:51:43 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>narissara.lol/journal/posts/8/</guid>
      <description>There&amp;rsquo;s a difference between looking and being, just like there&amp;rsquo;s a difference between hearing and listening.
Although the narrator have eyesight, he&amp;rsquo;s blind. It makes me wonder what I&amp;rsquo;m blinded by? Or what my friends are blinded by.
Miranda is a pretty self-aware person, but I don&amp;rsquo;t think she realized how she have no boundaries what so ever. She&amp;rsquo;s unable to set boundaries for herself. She doesn&amp;rsquo;t know how to directly tell people &amp;ldquo;no&amp;rdquo;, and it&amp;rsquo;s not typical for someone with a Mexican heritage.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
